Taha Hussien Abdelhameed Hassan

Web Developer

Address: Nasr City, Cairo, Egypt Phone: +201150651396 Email: ryhanytaha@gmail.com

OBJECTIVE

More two years of experience in developing websites in different web programming languages, I received a 6-months internship in a software company, then a one-month intensive training at the National Telecommunication Institute (NTI) in web development using Node Js and Angular.

looking for a web developer job, to gain more in depth skills and experience, to work in large websites, various tools and frameworks.

WORK EXPERIENCE

11/2018 - present

Web Developer, Advertizer Company, Nasr city

- Worked for a company as a web developer.
- Developing various landing pages, websites and single page applications from scratch.

04/2019 - present

Web Developer, freelancer

worked in many freelance projects with many clients for example:

- a cars website: http://golden-rents.com/
- moving furniture landing page: http://el3saly-trans.com/
- Advensco (software company): https://www.advensco.com/

EDUCATION

2014 - 2018

Bachelor's degree in science, Faculty of science, Al Azhar University.

Certified as a Web Developer, Node Js and Angular Certification, National Telecommunication Institute (NTI)

SKILLS

Technical:

- HTML5
- CSS3 SASS
- Bootstrap
- jQuery
- Java Script ECMA Script Type Script
- Node JS
- Angular framework
- React Js
- Wordpress
- Photoshop

language:

- English: good in listening, good in Writing, very good in reading and good in speaking
- Arabic: native lang.

PERSONAL SKILLS

Communication skills:

Gained through my experience as a web developer work with many freelance clients.

Problem solving:

Lots of problems happen while writing code, gained experiences in solving these problems.

• Time management:

Through my work and following the various courses and self-development, I was able to develop this skill.

• Teamwork:

I have acquired this skill on a graduate project and through working on various projects with other people.

PERSONAL INFORMAION

Date of birth: 01/01/1997Nationality: Egyption

Marital status: Single Military service: Exemption

Links

• LinkedIn: www.linkedin.com/in/taharehany

• Github: https://github.com/taharehany

• Facebook: www.facebook.com/taha.rehany

• Website: www.rehany.site

REFERENCES

References and Certificates are upon under request.